Joyce Carol Oates Papers
Joyce Carol Oates Papers
- Correspondence-subject files
  - Gordon, Mary (Box 6)
  - Goreau, Angeline (Box 6)
  - Gornick, Vivian (Box 6)
  - Gotham Book Mart & Gallery, Inc. (Box 6)
  - Gottlieb, Robert (Box 6)
  - Goyen, William (Box 6)
  - Graham, Elizabeth (Box 6)
  - Graham, Mark (Box 6)
  - Grand Street (Box 6)
  - Granta (Box 6)
  - Grass, Gunter (Box 6)
  - Gray, Francine (Box 6)
  - Greco, Loretta (Box 6)
  - Greeley, Andrew M. (Box 6)
  - Greenberg, Georgia Shreve (Box 6)
  - Greenberg, Martin H. (Box 6)
  - Greenblatt, Ellen (Box 6)
  - [Robert] Greenwald Productions, Inc. (Box 6)
  - Greer, Germaine (Box 6)
  - [Blanche C.] Gregory, Inc. (Box 6)
  - Grimsley, Jim (Box 6)
  - Grissom, Colleen (Box 6)
  - Grobel, Larry (Box 6)
  - Guare, John (Box 6)
  - Gubar, Susan (Box 6)
  - Gruen, Arno (Box 6)
  - Guerard, Albert J. (Box 6)
  - [John Simon] Guggenheim Memorial Foundation (Box 6)
  - Guilhamet, Leon (Box 6)
  - Guiliano, Edward (Box 6)
  - Gupta, Sunetra (Box 6)
  - Guterson, David (Box 6)
  - Gutkind, Lee (Box 6)
  - Gutmann, Amy (Box 6)
  - Guttfreund, Andre (Box 6)
  - Gwinn, Beth (Box 6)
  - H, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Haba, James (Box 6)
  - Hadas, Pamela White (Box 6)
  - Hall, Donald (Box 6)
  - Halpern, Daniel (Box 6)
  - Halpert, Sam (Box 6)
  - Hamid, Mohsin (Box 6)
  - Hancock, Geoff (Box 6)
  - Handman, Wynn, See American Place Theatre.
  - Hansell, Betsey (Box 6)
  - Hansen, Ron (Box 6)
  - Hansen, Stig, See Ordfront Magasin.
  - Hanson, David T. (Box 6)
  - Harbourfront Reading Series (Toronto) (Box 6)
  - Hardison, O. B. (Box 6)
  - Hardwich, Elizabeth (Box 6)
  - Harlow, Enid (Box 6)
  - Harper Collins, 4 folders (Box 7)
  - Harper's Magazine (Box 7)
  - Harpprecht, Klaus (Box 7)
  - Harris, Jana (Box 7)
  - Harvard Review (Box 7)
  - Harvey, Charles W. (Box 7)
  - Havazelet, Ehud (Box 7)
  - Havel, Vaclav (Box 7)
  - Hawkes, John (Box 7)
  - Hawkins, John, See John Hawkins & Associates, Inc..
  - Hayfield, Nancy (Box 7)
  - Hazzard, Shirley (Box 7)
  - Heath, William (Box 7)
  - Heavenridge, Cecily Smith (daughter of Catherine "Kay" Smith) (Box 7)
  - Hecht, Anthony (Box 7)
  - Heffernan, William (Box 7)
  - Hefner, Christie, See Playboy.
  - Hegi, Ursula (Box 7)
  - Heilbrun, Carolyn G. (Box 7)
  - Heim, Kathleen (Box 7)
  - Heller, Erich (Box 7)
  - Heller, Joseph (Box 7)
  - Hellman, Lillian (Box 7)
  - Helprin, Mark (Box 7)
  - Hempel, Amy (Box 7)
  - Henderson, Bill, See Pushcart Press.
  - Henry, DeWitt (Box 7)
  - Henslee, Helen (Box 7)
  - Herendeen, Ed, See Contemporary American Theatre Festival.
  - Hess, Edward (Box 7)
  - Heyen, William, 5 folders (Box 7)
  - Higgins, Judith (Box 7)
  - [David] Higham Associates (Box 7)
  - Hilberry, Conrad (Box 7)
  - Hill, Lawrence (Box 7)
  - Hills, Rust, See Esquire.
  - Hirsch, Edward (Box 7)
  - Hoagland, Ted (Box 7)
  - Hoch, Edward D. (Box 7)
  - Hoffman, Arthur W. (Box 7)
  - Hoffman, Daniel (Box 7)
  - Hollander, John (Box 7)
  - Hollis, Leo, See Fourth Estate.
  - Holloway, Julia Bolton (Box 7)
  - Holmes, Charlotte (Box 7)
  - Holt, Rinehart and Winston (Box 7)
  - Holub, Miroslav (Box 7)
  - Homes, A. M. (Box 7)
  - Honig, Lucy (Box 7)
  - Hood, Ann (Box 7)
  - Hopler, Jay (Box 7)
  - Horgan, Paul (Box 7)
  - Horne, Lewis (Box 7)
  - Hornsey, Richard (Box 7)
  - Horowitz, Irving Louis (Box 7)
  - Horror Writers Association (Box 7)
  - Hortin, David (Box 7)
  - Houghton Mifflin Company (Box 7)
  - House, Gordon (see: BBC) (Box 7)
  - Houston, Julie (Box 7)
  - Howard, Ben (Box 7)
  - Howard, Maureen (Box 7)
  - Howard, Richard (Box 7)
  - Howarth, William (Box 7)
  - Howe, Irving (Box 7)
  - Hudgins, Andrew (Box 7)
  - The Hudson Review (Box 7)
  - Hughes, Daniel (Box 7)
  - Hughes, Katherine Nouri (Box 7)
  - Hughes, Ted (Box 7)
  - Hunt, Gordon (Box 7)
  - Hunter, Evan (Box 7)
  - Hynes, Samuel Lynn (Box 7)
  - Hyperion (Box 7)
  - I (Box 7)
  - Ignatow, David (Box 7)
  - Ignatow, Rose Graubart (Box 7)
  - International Creative Management, Inc. (Box 7)
  - International eBook Award Foundation (Box 7)
  - International Institute of Modern Letters (Box 7)
  - Israel, Calvin (Box 7)
  - Iverson, Brad (Box 7)
  - Izvestia (Известия) (Box 7)
  - J (Box 7)
  - Jackson, Nagle (Box 7)
  - Jackson, Thomas F. (Box 7)
  - Jackson, Thomas F., "The Triumph of the Spider Monkey", screenplay (Box 7)
  - Jacobs, Loraine and Jim (Box 7)
  - Jacobsen, Josephine (Box 7)
  - Jaffee, Annette Williams (Box 7)
  - Jakes, John (Box 7)
  - Janowitz, Tama (Box 7)
  - Jenks, Tom (Box 7)
  - Jennings, Dana Andrew (Box 7)
  - John Hawkins & Associates, Inc., 4 folders (Box 7)
  - Johnson, Charles (Box 8)
  - Johnson, Diane (Box 8)
  - Johnson, Greg, 21 folders (Box 8)
  - Johnson, Jef (Box 8)
  - Johnson, Joyce and J. Seward, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Jones, Edward P. (Box 8)
  - Jones, Landon Y. (Box 8)
  - Jones, Neal T. (Box 8)
  - Jones, Robert (Box 8)
  - Jones, Thom (Box 8)
  - Jong, Erica (Box 8)
  - Jordan, Shirley M. (Box 8)
  - Joseph, Lawrence and Nancy Van Goethem (Box 8)
  - Junker, Howard (Box 8)
  - Jurik, Lubos (Box 8)
  - K (Box 8)
  - Kadish, Rachel (Box 8)
  - Kahn, Wolf (Box 8)
  - Kakutani, Michiko (Box 8)
  - Kalman, Judith (Box 8)
  - Kalpakian, Laura (Box 8)
  - Kaminsky, Stuart M., See Mystery Writers of America.
  - Kane, Katherine (Box 8)
  - Kaniecki, Michael (Box 8)
  - Karl, Frederick Robert (Box 8)
  - Karlin, Wayne (Box 8)
  - Karr, Mary (Box 8)
  - Kauffmann, Stanley (Box 8)
  - Kaufman, Bel (Box 8)
  - Kaufmann, Myron S. (Box 8)
  - Kaufmann, Walter (Box 8)
  - Kazin, Alfred (Box 8)
  - Keeley, Edmund, 3 folders (Box 8)
  - Keenan, Deborah (Box 9)
  - Keithley, George (Box 9)
  - Kelly, M. T. (Box 9)
  - Kenedi, Aaron (Box 9)
  - Kennedy, William (Box 9)
  - Kennedy, X. J. (Box 9)
  - Kenney, Susan (Box 9)
  - The Kenyon Review (Box 9)
  - Kercheval, Jesse Lee (Box 9)
  - Kesselman, Wendy Ann (Box 9)
  - Kessler, Joan C. (Box 9)
  - Kilberg, Garnett, See Cohen, Garnett Kilberg.
  - King, Stephen (Box 9)
  - Kinsella, W. P. (Box 9)
  - Kitaj, R. B. (Box 9)
  - Kizer, Carolyn (Box 9)
  - Klopp, Karyl (Box 9)
  - Knebel, Fletcher (Box 9)
  - Knowlton, Grace (Box 9)
  - Koch, Stephen (Box 9)
  - Koepp, Donald W. (Box 9)
  - Koestenbaum, Phyllis (Box 9)
  - Koestenbaum, Wayne (Box 9)
  - Kohler, Sheila (Box 9)
  - Kollek, Teddy (Box 9)
  - Komunyakaa, Yusef (Box 9)
  - Koplas, John S. (Box 9)
  - Korelitz, Jean Hanff (Box 9)
  - Kossman, Nina (Box 9)
  - Kotker, Zane (Box 9)
  - Kramer, Peter D. (Box 9)
  - Krapf, Norbert (Box 9)
  - Krementz, Jill (Box 9)
  - Kricorian, Nancy (Box 9)
  - Krois, Erich (Box 9)
  - Kulka, John (Box 9)
  - Kumin, Maxine (Box 9)
  - Kunitz, Stanley and Eise (Box 9)
  - Kuryluk, Ewa (Box 9)
  - L, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - L. A. Theatre Works (Box 9)
  - Lapautre, Michelle (Box 9)
  - LaRiche, William (Box 9)
  - Larriere, Claire, See Paris Transcontinental.
  - LaSalle, Peter (Box 9)
  - Laskin, David (Box 9)
  - Laughlin, James (Box 9)
  - Laurence, Margaret (Box 9)
  - Lauterbach, Ann (Box 9)
  - Lavin, Irving and Marilyn (Box 9)
  - Lawford, Patricia Kennedy (Box 9)
  - Layton, Aviva (Box 9)
  - Layton, Irving (Box 9)
  - Lazar, Liliane (Box 9)
  - Lea, Sydney (Box 9)
  - Leavitt, Alan J. (Box 9)
  - Leavitt, David (Box 9)
  - Lee, Chang-rae (Box 9)
  - Leebron, Fred (Box 9)
  - Lefanu, Sarah (Box 9)
  - LeGuin, Ursula K. (Box 9)
  - Lehman, David (Box 9)
  - Leigh, Lona, See McManus, Lona Leigh.
  - Leithauser, Brad (Box 9)
  - Leland, Christopher T. (Box 9)
  - Lempert, Peter (Box 9)
  - Lentricchia, Frank (Box 9)
  - Leonard, Elmore (Box 9)
  - Leonard, George B. (Box 9)
  - Lerner, Michael, See Tikkun.
  - Lesley, Craig (Box 9)
  - Lessing, Doris (Box 9)
  - Letizia, Claudia V. (Box 9)
  - Levao, Ronald (Box 9)
  - Levertov, Denise (Box 9)
  - Levi, Jonathan (Box 9)
  - Levin, Gail (Box 9)
  - Levin, Marj Jackson (Box 9)
  - Levine, Philip (Box 9)
  - Levinson, Jerrold (Box 9)
  - Lewis, Reginald Sinclair (Box 9)
  - Lewis, Stephen (Box 9)
  - L'Heureux, John (Box 9)
  - The Library of America (Box 9)
  - Lietz, Robert (Box 9)
  - Lightman, Alan P. (Box 9)
  - Ligotti, Thomas (Box 9)
  - Liman, Claude (Box 9)
  - Lindberg, Stanley W., See The Georgia Review.
  - Linney, Romulus (Box 9)
  - Lipson, Brian (Box 9)
  - Lisle, Laurie (Box 9)
  - Literaturen (Box 9)
  - Little, Brown (Box 9)
  - Litz, A. Walton (Box 9)
  - Litzinger, Boyd (Box 9)
  - Locher-Lawrence, Werner (Box 9)
  - Lodge, David (Box 9)
  - Loeb, Monica (Box 9)
  - Lowenberg, Susan Albert, See L. A. Theatre Works.
  - Logan, Fritz (Box 9)
  - Logan, John (Box 9)
  - Long, David (Box 9)
  - Long Wharf Theatre (New Haven, CT) (Box 9)
  - Lopate, Phillip (Box 9)
  - Lopez, Barry Holstun (Box 9)
  - Lord John Press, See Yellin, Herb.
  - Los Angeles Theatre Academy, See Rossi, Al.
  - Los Angeles Times (Box 9)
  - Louisiana State University Press (Box 9)
  - Lowy, Bernard (Box 9)
  - Ludwig, Richard M. (Box 9)
  - Lundkvist, Arthur (Box 9)
  - Lurie, Alison (Box 9)
  - Luvaas, William (Box 9)
  - Lyden, Jacki (Box 9)
  - M, 3 folders (Box 9)
  - Malzberg, Barry (Box 10)
  - Mandelbaum, Paul (Box 10)
  - Manhattan Theatre Club (Box 10)
  - Mann, Emily, See McCarter Theatre.
  - Mano, D. Keith (Box 10)
  - Manoa (Box 10)
  - Marion Boyars Publishers Ltd. (Box 10)
  - Marshall, James M. (Box 10)
  - Marshall, Tom (Box 10)
  - Martin, Charles (Box 10)
  - Martin, John (Box 10)
  - Martin, Steve (Box 10)
  - [Elisabeth] Marton Agency (Box 10)
  - Mason, Bobbie Ann (Box 10)
  - Mason, David (Box 10)
  - Masterson, Dan (Box 10)
  - Matera, Lia (Box 10)
  - Matthews, William (Box 10)
  - Maxwell, William (Box 10)
  - Mazzaro, Jerome (Box 10)
  - McAuliffe, Jody (Box 10)
  - McBride, Mekeel (Box 10)
  - McCaffrey, Larry (Box 10)
  - McCann, Colum (Box 10)
  - McCarter Theatre (Princeton, NJ) (Box 10)
  - McCarthy, Cormac (Box 10)
  - McCarthy, Eugene J. (Box 10)
  - McClain, Rick (Box 10)
  - McClatchy, J. D. (Box 10)
  - McDaniels, Drucie (Box 10)
  - McEnroe, Colin (Box 10)
  - McGee, Lynn (Box 10)
  - McKeown, Tom (Box 10)
  - McLaughlin, Ruth (Box 10)
  - McManus, Lona Leigh (Box 10)
  - McMillan, Terry (Box 10)
  - McMillen, Sheila (Box 10)
  - McNamara, Eugene (Box 10)
  - McPherson, William (Box 10)
  - McPhillips, Robert (Box 10)
  - Meadow, Lynne, See Manhattan Theatre Club.
  - Means, David (Box 10)
  - Meek, Jay (Box 10)
  - Meeropol, Michael (Box 10)
  - Mehlman, Jeffrey (Box 10)
  - Meisel, Perry (Box 10)
  - Mellen, Joan (Box 10)
  - Melnyczuk, Arnold, See Agni.
  - Menguc, Sara (Box 10)
    See also [David] Higham Associates.
  - Menz, Katherine (Box 10)
  - Merchant Ivory Productions (Box 10)
  - Merwin, William Stanley (Box 10)
  - Metcalf, John (Box 10)
  - Michael Siegel & Associates, See Siegel, Michael.
  - Michaels, Leonard (Box 10)
  - Michaud, Marc A., See Necronomicon Press.
  - Michigan Quarterly Review, See Goldstein, Laurence.
  - Micklin Silver, Joan, See Silver, Joan Micklin.
  - Middlebrook, Diane Wood (Box 10)
  - Milazzo, Lee (Box 10)
  - Miles, Julia, See Women's Project.
  - Miller, Arthur (Box 10)
  - Miller, John (Box 10)
  - Millett, Kate (Box 10)
  - Miner, Earl Roy (Box 10)
  - Minkoff, George Robert (Box 10)
  - Miranda, Gary (Box 10)
  - Mirsky, Mark, See Fiction.
  - The Missouri Review (Box 10)
  - Mitchell, Lee Clark (Box 10)
  - Mitgang, Esther (Box 10)
  - Mizejewski, Linda (Box 10)
  - Moch, Cheryl (Box 10)
  - Modern Library, See Random House.
  - Mogan, Jewel (Box 10)
  - Molesworth, Charles (Box 10)
  - Molinaro, Elaine (Box 10)
  - Montague, John (Box 10)
  - Monteiro, George (Box 10)
  - Moore, Jack B. (Box 10)
  - Moore, Lorrie (Box 10)
  - Moore, Richard (Box 10)
  - Moorhead, Richard S. (Box 10)
  - Moreau, Jeanne (Box 10)
  - Morgan, Frederick, See The Hudson Review.
  - Morgan, James (Box 10)
  - Morgenthau, Robert M. (Box 10)
  - Morri, Brian (Box 10)
  - Morris, David B. (Box 10)
  - Morris, Mary (Box 10)
  - Morris, Mary McGarry (Box 10)
  - Morris, William (Box 10)
  - Morrison, Toni (Box 10)
  - Morrow, Bradford (Box 10)
  - Mort, John (Box 10)
  - Moser, Barry (Box 10)
  - Mosley, Walter (Box 10)
  - Mount Holyoke College (Box 10)
  - Mukand, Jon (Box 10)
  - Mukherjee, Bharati (Box 10)
  - Muldoon, Paul (Box 10)
  - Murray, Joan (Box 10)
  - Muske, Carol (Box 10)
  - Muzio, Gloria, See Circle Repertory Company.
  - Myers, Robert (Box 10)
  - Myerson, Julie (Box 10)
  - Mystery Writers of America (Box 10)
  - N (Box 10)
  - Nasar, Sylvia (Box 10)
  - The Nation (Box 10)
  - National Book Awards (Box 10)
  - Naylor, Gloria (Box 10)
  - Necronomicon Press (Box 10)
  - Nelson, Betty Palmer (Box 10)
  - Nemerov, Howard (Box 10)
  - Nemett, Adam (Box 11)
  - Nerve (Box 11)
  - New Directions (Box 11)
  - New Letters (University of Missouri - Kansas City) (Box 11)
  - The New Republic (Box 11)
  - New York Public Library (Box 11)
  - The New York Quarterly (Box 11)
  - The New York Review of Books (Box 11)
  - The New York Times (Box 11)
  - The New Yorker (Box 11)
  - Newhouse, Susan and Donald (Box 11)
  - Newman, Charles (Box 11)
  - Newman, Paul S. (Box 11)
  - Nikitas, Derek (Box 11)
  - Norman, Howard (Box 11)
  - Northwestern University Department of Theatre (Box 11)
  - [W. W.] Norton & Company (Box 11)
  - Nowlan, Alden (Box 11)
  - Nussbaum, Martha (Box 11)
  - O (Box 11)
  - O'Brien, Tim (Box 11)
  - Ochester, Ed (Box 11)
  - O'Connor, Philip F. (Box 11)
  - Odom, Mel (Box 11)
  - Offult, Chris (Box 11)
  - The Ohio Review (Box 11)
  - Olcott, Nick (Box 11)
  - Olds, Sharon (Box 11)
  - Oliver, Mary (Box 11)
  - Olsen, Sondra Spatt (Box 11)
  - Olsen, Tillie (Box 11)
  - Omni, See Datlow, Ellen.
  - O'Nan, Stewart (Box 11)
  - Onassis, Jacqueline Kennedy, See Doubleday.
  - Ondaatje, Michael (Box 11)
  - Ontario Arts Council (Box 11)
  - Opera Festival of New Jersey (Box 11)
  - Oppenheimer, judy (Box 11)
  - Ordfront Magasin (Box 11)
  - Orr, Greg, See Virginia Quarterly Review.
  - Ostriker, Alicia (Box 11)
  - Osztovits, Levente (Box 11)
  - Oxford University Press (Box 11)
  - Oz, Amos (Box 11)
  - Ozick, Cynthia (Box 11)
  - P, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Pacernik, Gary (Box 11)
  - Pagels, Elaine H. (Box 11)
  - Painter, Nell Irvin (Box 11)
  - Palumbo, Tom (Box 11)
  - Parcerisas, Francesc (Box 11)
  - Parini, Jay (Box 11)
  - The Paris Review (Box 11)
  - Paris Transcontinental (Box 11)
  - Park, Christine (Box 11)
  - Parker, Alan Michael (Box 11)
  - Partisan Review (Box 11)
  - Parva, Michael (Box 11)
  - Paschval, Dean (Box 11)
  - Patten, Robert L. (Box 11)
  - Payne, John R. (Box 11)
  - Peacock, Molly (Box 11)
  - Pearlman, Mickey (Box 11)
  - PEN American Center (Box 11)
  - PEN/Faulkner Award for Fiction (Box 11)
  - PEN Syndicated Fiction Project (Box 11)
  - Penguin Putnam, Inc. (Box 11)
  - Penlight Theater (Minneapolis, MN) (Box 11)
  - Penn, Barbara Allison (Box 11)
  - Penner, Jonathan (Box 11)
  - Penney, Charles Rand (Box 11)
  - Penzler, Otto, 3 folders (Box 11)
  - Pepper, James (Box 11)
  - Percy, Walker (Box 11)
  - Perkins, John (Box 11)
  - Perloff, Marjorie (Box 11)
  - Perlongo, Robert A. (Box 11)
  - Petesch, Natalie L. M. (Box 11)
  - Petrie, Graham (Box 11)
  - Petrie, Paul James (Box 11)
  - Pett, Stephen (Box 11)
  - Pezzotta, Alberto (Box 11)
  - Philadelphia Festival Theatre for New Plays (Box 12)
  - Phillips, Jayne Ann (Box 12)
  - Phillips, Mark (Box 12)
  - Phillips, Matt (Box 12)
  - Phillips, Robert S., 23 folders (Box 12)
  - Piel, Gerard (Box 12)
  - Pinckney, Darryl (Box 12)
  - Pinsker, Sanford (Box 12)
  - Pinsky, Robert (Box 12)
  - Piotrowski, Dallas (Box 12)
  - Piper, Adrian (Box 12)
  - Playboy (Box 12)
  - Pleşea, Gabriel (Box 12)
  - Plimpton, George, See The Paris Review.
  - Ploughshares (Box 12)
  - Plume, See Penguin Putnam, Inc..
  - Plumly, Stanley (Box 12)
  - Plummer, William (Box 12)
  - Poetry (Box 12)
  - Poetry Center (New York, NY), See Unterberg Poetry Center.
  - Poets & Writers (Box 12)
  - Poirier, Richard, See Raritan.
  - Pollinger, Murray (Box 12)
  - Pollitt, Katha (Box 12)
  - Porter, Alex (Box 12)
  - Porter, Joseph Ashby (Box 12)
  - Porter, Melinda Camby (Box 12)
  - Portmann, John (Box 12)
  - Pounds, Wayne (Box 12)
  - Poverman, C. E. (Box 12)
  - Prairie Schooner (Box 12)
  - Prescott, Peter S. (Box 12)
  - Press (Box 12)
  - Price, Reynolds (Box 12)
  - Princeton University, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Princeton University Press (Box 12)
  - Prior, Amy (Box 12)
  - Pritchard, Melissa (Box 12)
  - Pritchard, William H. (Box 12)
  - Proffer, Carl R. (Box 12)
  - Provincetown Theater Company (Box 12)
  - Prytz, Carl Frederick (Box 12)
  - Pulitzer Prize (Box 12)
  - Punch (Box 12)
  - Pushcart Press (Box 12)
  - Pynn, Nelia A. (Box 12)
  - Q (Box 12)
  - Qualls, Barry (Box 12)
  - Quintana, Ricardo (Box 12)
  - R, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Rabin, Arnold (Box 12)
  - Raine, Barry (Box 12)
  - Ramke, Bin (Box 12)
  - Ramsey Jarold (Box 12)
  - Ramsland, Katherine (Box 12)
  - Ranard, John (Box 12)
  - Random House, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Raritan (Box 13)
  - Rattner, Ruth (Box 13)
  - Ratzan, Richard M. (Box 13)
  - Ray, David (Box 13)
  - Rea Award (Box 13)
  - Reddy, Maureen T. (Box 13)
  - Redmon, Anne (Box 13)
  - Reed, John Robert, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Reed, Kit (Box 13)
  - Reibetanz, John (Box 13)
  - Reich, Charles (Box 13)
  - Reisman, Nancy (Box 13)
  - Rendell, Ruth (Box 13)
  - Renfield, Elinor (Box 13)
  - Revell, Donald (Box 13)
  - Rhodes, Richard (Box 13)
  - Ribalow, Harold Uriel (Box 13)
  - Ricci, Claudia (Box 13)
  - Richardson, James (Box 13)
  - Richman, Steven M. (Box 13)
  - Robbins, Henry, See [E. P.] Dutton.
  - Robbins, Mary Susannah (Box 13)
  - Roberts, Daniel, See Press.
  - Robertson, Mary Elsie (Box 13)
  - Robinson, Sally (Box 13)
  - Rocamora, Carol (Box 13)
  - Rodriguez, Miguel (Box 13)
  - Roger, Bruce Holland (Box 13)
  - Roper, Robert (Box 13)
  - Rorem, Ned (Box 13)
  - Rosen, Norman (Box 13)
  - Rosen, Richard Dean (Box 13)
  - Rosenberg, David (Box 13)
  - Rosenblatt, Roger (Box 13)
  - Rosenbluth, Sally (Box 13)
  - Rosenstone / Wender (Box 13)
  - Rosenthal, Lois, See Story.
  - Rosenthal, Macha Louis (Box 13)
  - Rossi, Al (Box 13)
  - Rossiter, Sarah (Box 13)
  - Rossner, Judith (Box 13)
  - Roszak, Theodore (Box 13)
  - Roth, Philip (Box 13)
  - Royle, Nicholas (Box 13)
  - Rozan, S. J. (Box 13)
  - Rubin, Gay (Box 13)
  - Rudenstine, Angelica Zander (Box 13)
  - Rudenstine, Neil L. (Box 13)
  - Rudman, Mark (Box 13)
  - Rumaker, Michael (Box 13)
  - Running Press (Box 13)
  - Ruth, Anne (Box 13)
  - S, 4 folders (Box 13)
  - Sacks, Peter (Box 13)
  - Safire, William (Box 13)
  - Said, Edward K. (Box 13)
  - St. Just, Maria (Box 13)
  - Saiter, Susan Sullivan (Box 13)
  - Salter, James (Box 13)
  - Samuel French, Inc. (Box 13)
  - Sanders, Nancy Dalton (Box 13)
  - Saner, Reg (Box 13)
  - Sanford J. Greenburger Associates, Inc. (Box 13)
  - Sapienza, Anthony, See The Spook Magazine.
  - Sarrantonio, Al (Box 13)
  - Saroyan, William (Box 13)
  - Sayre, Robert F. (Box 13)
  - Scanlan, Dick (Box 13)
  - Schaeffner, Susan Fromberg (Box 13)
  - Schaller, Barry R. (Box 13)
  - Scher, William (Box 13)
  - Schiller, Lawrence (Box 13)
  - Schinto, Jeanne (Box 13)
  - Schlimm, John E. (Box 13)
  - Schnabel, William (Box 13)
  - Schnack, Elisbeth (Box 13)
  - Schneider, Nina (Box 13)
  - Schneider, Ursula W. (Box 13)
  - Schulman, Grace (Box 13)
  - Schwartz, Lynn Sharon (Box 13)
  - Schwartz, Rhoda, See The American Poetry Review.
  - Scorsese, Martin (Box 13)
  - Scott, Joanna (Box 13)
  - Scruton, Roger (Box 13)
  - Seabrook, John (Box 13)
  - Searle, Elizabeth (Box 13)
  - Seattle Mime Theatre (Box 13)
  - Seban, Claude (Box 13)
  - See, Carolyn (Box 13)
  - Seebolm, Caroline (Box 13)
  - Selby, David (Box 13)
  - Sertner, Robert M. (Box 13)
  - Settle, Mary Lee (Box 13)
  - Sexton, Anne (Box 13)
  - Shaffron, Robert (Box 13)
  - Shankar, Radhika R. (Box 13)
  - Shapard, Robert (Box 13)
  - Shapiro, Dani (Box 13)
  - Shapiro, David (Box 13)
  - Shapiro, Harold T. (Box 13)
  - Shapiro, Jane (Box 13)
  - Shapiro, Karl Jay (Box 13)
  - Shapiro, Michael (Box 13)
  - Share Our Strength (Box 13)
  - Sharma, Akhil (Box 13)
  - Sharon Stage (Sharon, CT) (Box 13)
  - Sharp, Jan (Box 13)
  - Sharp, Ronald A., See The Kenyon Review.
  - Sheck, Laurie (Box 13)
  - Shepard, Jim (Box 13)
  - Sher, Jena (Box 13)
  - Sherry, Norman (Box 13)
  - Sherwood, Madeline (Box 13)
  - Showalter, Elaine and English, 4 folders (Box 13A)
  - Showalter, Jean (Box 13A)
  - Shreve, Elizabeth (Box 13A)
  - Shreve, Susan Richards (Box 13A)
  - Shrifte, Evelyn, See Vanguard Press, Inc..
  - Shulman, Alex Kates (Box 13A)
  - Shuttleworth, Paul (Box 13A)
  - Shwartz, Ronald B. (Box 13A)
  - Sidel, Elly, See John Hawkins & Associates, Inc..
  - Siegel, Michael (Box 13A)
  - Siegel, Rosalie (Box 13A)
  - Silesky, Barry (Box 13A)
  - Silet, Loring (Box 13A)
  - Silver, Joan Micklin (Box 13A)
  - Silver, Nicky (Box 13A)
  - Silvis, Randall (Box 13A)
  - Simic, Charles (Box 13A)
  - Simon, Rachel (Box 13A)
  - Simpson, Eileen (Box 13A)
  - Singer, Peter (Box 13A)
  - Sipper, Ralph B. (Box 13A)
  - Sjoberg, Leif (Box 13A)
  - Sjöstrand, Östen (Box 13A)
  - Skyler, Lisanne (Box 13A)
  - Skyler, Lisanne and Tristine, Getting to Know All About You, screen adaptation (Box 13A)
  - Slate (Box 13A)
  - Slavitt, David R. (Box 13A)
  - Sluckis, Mykolas (Box 13A)
  - Smedick, Lois K., 2 folders (Box 13A)
  - Smith, Ali (Box 13A)
  - Smith, Catherine "Kay", 2 folders (Box 13A)
  - Smith, Charlie (Box 13A)
  - Smith, Dave (Box 13A)
  - Smith, Leonora (Box 13A)
  - Smith, Mark (Box 13A)
  - Smith, Martha Nell (Box 13A)
  - Smith, Mary-Ann Tirone (Box 13A)
  - Smith, Michael A. (Box 13A)
  - Smith, William Jay (Box 13A)
  - Smith and Kraus, Inc. (Box 13A)
  - Smith College (Box 13A)
  - Snake Nation Press (Box 13A)
  - Snider, Norman (Box 13A)
  - Sobczak, John (Box 13A)
  - Sobel, Richard (Box 13A)
  - Sokolov, Raymond (Box 13A)
  - Sontag, Susan (Box 13A)
  - The South Bank Centre (London, Eng.) (Box 13A)
  - Souther, Randy (Box 13A)
  - The Southern Review (Box 13A)
  - Southwest Review (Box 13A)
  - Spacks, Barry (Box 13A)
  - Speakers Worldwide, Inc. (Box 13A)
  - Speer, Laurel (Box 13A)
  - Spencer, Elizabeth (Box 13A)
  - Spencer, Stuart (Box 13A)
  - The Spencer Library (Box 13A)
  - Spender, Stephen, See AIDS Crisis Trust.
  - Spilka, Mark (Box 13A)
  - The Spook Magazine (Box 13A)
  - Sreelakshmi, P. (Box 13A)
  - Stafford, William (Box 13A)
  - Stallworth, Anne Nall (Box 13A)
  - Stand (Box 13A)
  - Stanford, Donald E., See The Southern Review.
  - Stanlis, Peter James (Box 13A)
  - Stansberry, Domenic (Box 13A)
  - Stansell, Christine (Box 13A)
  - Stansky, Peter (Box 13A)
  - Starer, Robert (Box 13A)
  - Starn, Frances (Box 13A)
  - Staub, Augustus W., See University of Georgia.
  - Stearns, Gordon W. (Box 13A)
  - Steele, Jadrien Ford (Box 13A)
  - Stegmuller, Francis (Box 13A)
  - Steinbach, Alice (Box 13A)
  - Steinberg, Rafael (Box 13A)
  - Steiner, George (Box 13A)
  - Stephens, Michael (Box 13A)
  - Stern, Daniel (Box 13A)
  - Stern, Gerald (Box 13A)
  - Stern, Richard (Box 13A)
  - Sterneck, Wolfgang (Box 13A)
  - Stevens, Holly (Box 13A)
  - Stewart, Lucretia (Box 13A)
  - Stewart, Ronald S. (Box 13A)
  - Stickney, Brandon M. (Box 13A)
  - Stiles, Martha Bennett (Box 13A)
  - Still, James (Box 13A)
  - Stitt, Peter, See The Gettysburg Review.
  - Stollman, Aryeh Lev (Box 13A)
  - Stone, Clifford (Box 13A)
  - Stone, Robert (Box 13A)
  - Stony Brook- Millstone Watershed Association (Pennington, NJ) (Box 13A)
  - Story (Box 13A)
  - Storylines America (Box 13A)
  - Straight, Susan (Box 13A)
  - Strand, Mark (Box 13A)
  - Strandberg, Victor (Box 13A)
  - Strassburger, John (Box 13A)
  - Straub, Peter (Box 13A)
  - Strauss, Darin (Box 13A)
  - Strout, Elizabeth (Box 13A)
  - Studer, Stefan (Box 13A)